... The lifestream?
...I think I get it now.
Huh?
The planet's answer... the Promised Land...
It's where we can meet again... I think.
Yeah. Let's go there.
Oh yeah, what about the others?
Yo! Over here!
Looks like they're all safe! What a relief!
I'll be damned... They made it out in one piece.
But... what the hell do we do next?
Any minute now, Holy's gonna start working.
And when it does, this place'll be done for...
O Lady Luck... Don't fail me now.
Shiiit!
The flower lady?
Dammit!
What's gonna happen to Midgar?
Ain't there anythin' we can do!?
We've already evacuated everybody tae the slums.
But if this disnae let up...
Holy must not have made it in time.
The meteor's too close to the planet.
At this rate, Holy'll just make things worse.
Forget Midgar — the whole planet's in danger...
Over there!
What the hell's all this?...
... The lifestream.
She's here.